Rojan Dahal

Computer Engineer

An enthusiastic computer engineering undergraduate from the Nepal Engineering College. Possess programming skill in different programming languages with experience in Full Stack Development using JavaScript Framework and Experience in android app development using Java. I am a person craving to make career out of computer engineering. Further, I am very keen to add something valuable in my field by thoroughly researching the issue leading to life changing innovation.

x rojandahal2001@gmail.com

Rathmandu, Nepal

in linkedin.com/in/rojan-dahal

instagram.com/mrwhoisthisguy

9862230132

SKILLS

React Native

dahalrojan.com.np/

github.com/rojandahal

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Science and Engineering

Nepal Engineering College

2018 - 2023 3.70

10+2 Science

KantipurHigher Secondary School

2016 - 2018 3.54

SLC

Pokhariya Secondary School

2016 3.80

INTERNATIONAL PROJECT

B+NESDG (Bhutan+Nepal Higher Education for Accomplishing Sustainable Development Goals) (2022 - 2023)

Express

Microsoft Office

Java for Android Development

Student partner for the project and participated in Online meetings and events with students from partner countries to contribute to sustainable development goals.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Spotify Clone

- This is a spotify clone created with React and Firebase as backend
- The data are managed using simple JSON and it hosts intuitive design
- https://github.com/rojandahal/spotify-clone

Planka Task Manager Clone

- This is a Planka clone created with Nodejs and Fastify
- It uses ejs as templating engine and has Oauth with openId connect and Fastify for creating API
- https://github.com/rojandahal/ejs-fastify

Recipe Organizer Website

- Web app developed using React for frontend and NodeJS/ExpressJS for backend and MongoDB is used as database.
 It implements creation of API for frontend and fetching data using axios for API calls,
- https://github.com/rojandahal/recipe-organizer-app.

Bhaka Music Streaming Android App

- An android app developed for streaming flac and opus. Developed using Java and use of 3rd party library ExoPlayer for streaming music which is hosted in NodeJS server,
- https://github.com/rojandahal/bhaka-streaming-android-app.

Nepal Covid Android App

- An android app developed for tracking covid-19 cases developed in Java, includes Opendata API and implementation of Volley for REST api,
- https://github.com/rojandahal/Nepal-Covid-Updates-App.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Optimum Futurist Tech Pvt. Ltd (04/2023 - 07/2023) Software Engineer Intern

Web Tuned Studios (12/2023 - Present)

Fullstack Developer

CERTIFICATES

Android App Development Specialization (06/2021)

Course taken in Coursera for Android App development specialization: https://coursera.org/share/ddd29ab6994457418e7da91259f9cff8

LANGUAGES

Nepali

English

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

Full Professional Proficiency

INTERESTS

Software Development

Web Development

Android Development

Networking

ΑI